
const srcQuestions = [
  Question(
    category: Category.geography,
    question: "Cairo is the capital city of which country?",
    hint1: "E...",
    hint2: "E...t",
    answer: "Egypt",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.geography,
    question: "Which sea lies to the north of Turkey?",
    hint1: "B...",
    hint2: "B...k",
    answer: "Black",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.geography,
    question: "Which country has the capital city of Damascus?",
    hint1: "S...",
    hint2: "S...a",
    answer: "Syria",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.geography,
    question: "Which river runs through Paris?",
    hint1: "S...",
    hint2: "S...e",
    answer: "Seine",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.geography,
    question: "Accra is the capital city of which country?",
    hint1: "G...",
    hint2: "G...a",
    answer: "Ghana",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.history,
    question: "Which philosopher was Aristotle a student of?",
    hint1: "P...",
    hint2: "P...o",
    answer: "Plato",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.history,
    question:
        "What was the first colony established by the British in North America?",
    hint1: "J...",
    hint2: "J...wn",
    answer: "Jamestown",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.history,
    question: "What year did the Titanic sink?",
    hint1: "1...2",
    hint2: "19...2",
    answer: "1912",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.history,
    question: "Which ancient civilization invented papyrus?",
    hint1: "E...",
    hint2: "E...t",
    answer: "Egypt",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.history,
    question:
        "Sparta, Athens and Crete are all cities of which ancient empire?",
    hint1: "G...",
    hint2: "G...k",
    answer: "Greek",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.literature,
    question: "Who is the author of the dystopian novel \"1984\"?",
    hint1: "G... O...",
    hint2: "G...e O...ll",
    answer: "George Orwell",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.literature,
    question: "Which Russian author wrote the novel \"War and Peace\"?",
    hint1: "L... T...",
    hint2: "L...o T...oy",
    answer: "Leo Tolstoy",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.literature,
    question: "What is the name of Don Quixote's squire sidekick?",
    hint1: "S... P...",
    hint2: "S...o P...a",
    answer: "Sancho Panza",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.literature,
    question: "The Buendia family feature in which famous novel?",
    hint1: "O... H... Y... of S...",
    hint2: "O...e H...d Y...r of S...e",
    answer: "One Hundred Years of Solitude",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.literature,
    question: "Who wrote the war novel \"Death in the Afternoon\"?",
    hint1: "E... H...",
    hint2: "E...st H...ay",
    answer: "Ernest Hemingway",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.movie,
    question:
        "\"Say 'hello' to my little friend!\" is a famous quote from which crime movie?",
    hint1: "S...",
    hint2: "S...ce",
    answer: "Scarface",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.movie,
    question:
        "\"To infinity and beyond!\" is a catchphrase associated with which popular Disney-Pixar character?",
    hint1: "B... L...",
    hint2: "B...z L...r",
    answer: "Buzz Lightyear",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.movie,
    question: "What is the name of the scary clown in 2017 movie 'It'?",
    hint1: "P...",
    hint2: "P...ise",
    answer: "Pennywise",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.movie,
    question: "In which movie did Arnold Schwarzenegger say 'I'll be back'?",
    hint1: "T...",
    hint2: "T...or",
    answer: "Terminator",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.movie,
    question: "What is Captain America's main weapon?",
    hint1: "S...",
    hint2: "S...d",
    answer: "Shield",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.music,
    question:
        "Is a xylophone a wind, string, percussion, or keyboard instrument?",
    hint1: "P...",
    hint2: "P...n",
    answer: "Percussion",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.music,
    question: "\"In The End\" was a 2002 hit for which band?",
    hint1: "L... P...",
    hint2: "L...n P...k",
    answer: "Linkin Park",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.music,
    question: "Who created 'The Blue Danube'?",
    hint1: "J... S... II",
    hint2: "J...n S...s II",
    answer: "Johann Strauss II",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.music,
    question: "What nationality was the composer Carl Weber?",
    hint1: "G...",
    hint2: "G...n",
    answer: "German",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.music,
    question: "What is Sting's real name?",
    hint1: "G... S...",
    hint2: "G...n S...r",
    answer: "Gordon Sumner",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.science,
    question: "How many Laws of Thermodynamics are there?",
    hint1: "F...",
    hint2: "F...r",
    answer: "Four",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.science,
    question:
        "Who wrote the science law 'for every action there is an equal and opposite reaction'?",
    hint1: "I... N...",
    hint2: "I...c N...ton",
    answer: "Isaac Newton",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.science,
    question: "Which planet is the second largest planet in the Solar System?",
    hint1: "S...",
    hint2: "S...rn",
    answer: "Saturn",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.science,
    question:
        "What is the side of the triangle opposite the right angle, according to Pythagoras?",
    hint1: "H...",
    hint2: "Hy...use",
    answer: "Hypotenuse",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.science,
    question: "Which is the lightest of all the metallic elements?",
    hint1: "L...",
    hint2: "L...um",
    answer: "Lithium",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.sport,
    question: "Netherlands Football teams typically play in which color?",
    hint1: "O...",
    hint2: "O...ge",
    answer: "Orange",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.sport,
    question:
        "Lionel Messi has played his entire senior career with which European club?",
    hint1: "Ba...",
    hint2: "Ba...ona",
    answer: "Barcelona",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.sport,
    question:
        "A tennis match is divided into three or five groups, known as what?",
    hint1: "S...",
    hint2: "S...t",
    answer: "Set",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.sport,
    question: "A Marathon race is named after a place in which country?",
    hint1: "G...",
    hint2: "G...ce",
    answer: "Greece",
  ),
  Question(
    category: Category.sport,
    question: "Beginners in judo wear a belt of which color?",
    hint1: "W...",
    hint2: "W...te",
    answer: "White",
  ),
];
